A Guide to the Carl Pfaffman papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA190
Rockefeller Archive Center
Carl Pfaffman papers, Rockefeller University Faculty
1970-1980
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Pfaffmann, Carl
FA190
4 Cubic Feet 1 box, 1 volume, and 7 packages
1 box, 1 volume and 7 seven packages.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 450 P471
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Rockefeller University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Pfaffmann, Carl
- Personal-Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Public Relations (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Christmas Party & Conn. Picnic, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Personal Vita (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Christmas Party, Lab (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Personal-Pfaffman-Map (Conn) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Jokes (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Taste, Olfaction, and the Central Nervous System. A Festschrift in Honor of Carl Pfaffmann., 1985 (Volume 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Edited by Donald W. Pfaff. The Rockefeller University Press, New York, 1985
- Accounting records for Pfaffmann Laboratory, 1970-1980
  Scope and Contents note
  Monthly computer printout sheets. In 7 Packages.
  - 1970-1972, 1970-1973, 1970-1975, 1 (Package 1)
  - 1971-1973, 1972-1973, 1972-1975, 2 (Package 2)
  - 1973-1974, 3 (Package 3)
  - 1973-1976, 1974-1975, 1974-1976, 4 (Package 4)
  - 1975-1976, 1975-1980, 5 (Package 5)
  - 1976-1977, 1976-1979, 6 (Package 6)
  - 1977-1978, 1978-1979, 7 (Package 7)